<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Posts on sergio</title>
    <link>/post/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Posts on sergio</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 01 May 2020 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="/post/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>A toy engine. From 0 to Ludum Dare</title>
      <link>/post/2020/05/01/a-toy-engine.-from-0-to-ludum-dare/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 01 May 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/post/2020/05/01/a-toy-engine.-from-0-to-ludum-dare/</guid>
      <description>Last November I started working on a toy DX12 renderer. At first my intention was to add a new backend for Milton, but after I got the first triangle going it became pretty addictive to just keep going and see where I could take it. Here&amp;rsquo;s a write-up of what I&amp;rsquo;ve got going!
As I have grown this system, my main focus has been on API design and the core rendering API.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The current state of my compiler project</title>
      <link>/post/2018/08/04/the-current-state-of-my-compiler-project/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 04 Aug 2018 18:55:39 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/post/2018/08/04/the-current-state-of-my-compiler-project/</guid>
      <description>This is the second post about my C compiler, SCC. Look here for an index.
In the past couple of months I have been working on the compiler fairly regularly, in manageable 30-40 minute intervals about every day or so, and it has gotten to the point where I know that I can get a working C compiler by just putting in the hours.
This project has been like drinking from a firehose.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>I&#39;m making a compiler!</title>
      <link>/post/2017/05/10/im-making-a-compiler/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 10 May 2017 18:47:12 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/post/2017/05/10/im-making-a-compiler/</guid>
      <description>This is the first post about my C compiler, SCC. Look here for an index.
 It&amp;rsquo;s been almost 3 months since I joined Intel as a BIOS developer. I like it here, and mostly I&amp;rsquo;m relieved that later this year I will celebrate my 30th birthday and not be living in my parent&amp;rsquo;s house. Not that there&amp;rsquo;s anything wrong with that, but my sense of self-worth was starting to get hit because I was not being a productive member of the economy.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>How the Milton Renderer Works</title>
      <link>/post/2016/10/20/how-the-milton-renderer-works/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 20 Oct 2016 15:33:47 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/post/2016/10/20/how-the-milton-renderer-works/</guid>
      <description>Disclaimer: This document is not up-to-date. I will eventually write a new post that better reflects the current state of Milton, but in the mean time this is good enough.
After a long time in development, Milton has a brand new renderer. Before now, Milton did all of its rendering on the CPU. The new renderer uses OpenGL to take advantage of the GPU.
I didn&amp;rsquo;t expect to release OpenGL without problems.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>